(Amy:)Well, that's it.
(Amy:)For the next five weeks, we are
officially living together.
(Sheldon:)I guess the experiment begins.
We did it!
Yeah!
(Sheldon:)Which side of the bed
would you prefer?
(Amy:)Doesn't matter to me.
Your choice.
(Sheldon:)No, no, we're living together
now-- everything's equal.
(Sheldon:)You know? I know that I have
a tendency to be controlling,
(Sheldon:)so I would rather
you choose.
(Amy:)Well, Sheldon,
I really appreciate that,
(Amy:)but these things mean more
to you than they do to me,
(Amy:)so whatever you want.
(Sheldon:)Well, clearly,
it's not whatever I want,
(Sheldon:)because what I want is for you
to make this decision,
(Sheldon:)and you refuse to do that.
(Amy:)Well, I'm not refusing.
(Amy:)I'm just trying
to be considerate.
(Sheldon:)Like when you
let me get those shoes
(Sheldon:)with the wheels on the bottom,
(Sheldon:)and then watched me roll
right into traffic?
(Amy:)Sheldon, will you please
just pick a side?
(Sheldon:)Fine.